

Sultan Adeleke

FRONTEND DEVELOPER & TECHNICAL WRITER

☑ sultanadeleke6@gmail.com 🤳 08147855981 👂 No 29, Apena Street, Magbon Abeokuta

Profile

I am a success-driven, determined Front-end developer. I have experience using Html CSS and javaScript to build accessible component-based web pages and systems.

Ability to deliver quality results while collaborating in rapidly changing work environments and team compositions.

A passionate person willing to learn more technologies to become a better developer than I was yesterday. So determined and result oriented.

Education

B.sc Medical Physiology Nov 2017 - Sep 2021

OSUN STATE UNIVERSITY, OSOGBO

WEB DESIGNER Mar 2020 - Apr 2022

APTECH COMPUTER EDUCATION, IBADAN

Html-5, CSS3 & javaScript to Build Interactive Feb 2023 - Mar 2023

Web Pages.

YouAccel

SOFTWARE FRONTEND ENGINEERING Feb 2023 - Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING BOOTCAMP

Employment

FREELANCE TECHNICAL WRITER Oct 2022 - Present

FREELANCE FRONTEND DEVELOPER Nov 2020 - Present

Internships

FRONTEND DEVELOPER INTERN Mar 2023 - Present

LEARNNOWAFRICA

References

References available upon request.

Skills

Html-5, CSS3, javaScript, Tailwind, Jira, Confluence, git and github, React

Languages

English

Hobbies

■ Coding, Reading, Games

Qualities

■ Teamplayer, Effective Communication Skill, Good Listener, Higly organised and detail-oriented, Ability to meet deadlines